[{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664107985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16369,"timeElapsed":100169},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11382,"timeElapsed":111553},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":14159,"timeElapsed":125713},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664144929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11400,"timeElapsed":137113},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664153489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8559,"timeElapsed":145673},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664157521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":149705},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":153673},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664168593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":7104,"timeElapsed":160777},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":9767,"timeElapsed":170545},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":9255,"timeElapsed":181841},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6039,"timeElapsed":187881},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6279,"timeElapsed":194161},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5655,"timeElapsed":199817},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664212561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4927,"timeElapsed":204745},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664216153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3591,"timeElapsed":208337},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3887,"timeElapsed":212225},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664270993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":50951,"timeElapsed":263177},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":10015,"timeElapsed":273193},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":61000,"timeElapsed":342353},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":346665},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664361721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":7239,"timeElapsed":353905},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":7480,"timeElapsed":361385},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6135,"timeElapsed":367521},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664386665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":11327,"timeElapsed":378849},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4567,"timeElapsed":383417},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6871,"timeElapsed":390289},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664434097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":35991,"timeElapsed":426281},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":11199,"timeElapsed":439145},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":9455,"timeElapsed":448601},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664460849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":453033},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5992,"timeElapsed":459025},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5719,"timeElapsed":464745},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5439,"timeElapsed":470185},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664482321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4319,"timeElapsed":474505},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8183,"timeElapsed":482689},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664508057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":17552,"timeElapsed":500241},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664527417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":17407,"timeElapsed":519601},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6543,"timeElapsed":526145},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4391,"timeElapsed":530537},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664706089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":167735,"timeElapsed":698273},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664711497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5408,"timeElapsed":703681},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664721361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9863,"timeElapsed":713545},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664772016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":50654,"timeElapsed":764200},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664780713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8696,"timeElapsed":772897},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664795809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":15095,"timeElapsed":787993},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664883625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":86159,"timeElapsed":875809},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664891977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":8352,"timeElapsed":884161},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664900217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8239,"timeElapsed":892401},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664917849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":17631,"timeElapsed":910033},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664921738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3888,"timeElapsed":913921},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664930041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8303,"timeElapsed":922225},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664932825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2783,"timeElapsed":925009},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664936513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3688,"timeElapsed":928697},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664940057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":932241},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664950041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8631,"timeElapsed":942225},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664953017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2975,"timeElapsed":945201},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664958729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5711,"timeElapsed":950913},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664961953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":954137},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664966065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4111,"timeElapsed":958249},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664978202,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12136,"timeElapsed":970386},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664982617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4415,"timeElapsed":974801},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664985513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2895,"timeElapsed":977697},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664988801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3286,"timeElapsed":980985},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664993441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4640,"timeElapsed":985625},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665001272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6207,"timeElapsed":993456},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665003953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":996137},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665007265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3312,"timeElapsed":999449},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665010865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":1003049},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665014113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3247,"timeElapsed":1006297},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665018801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4687,"timeElapsed":1010985},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3120,"timeElapsed":1014106},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665025713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3791,"timeElapsed":1017897},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665031145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5431,"timeElapsed":1023329},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665047345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14687,"timeElapsed":1039529},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665050553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3207,"timeElapsed":1042737},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665054385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":1046569},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665064066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9680,"timeElapsed":1056250},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665067977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":1060161},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665073457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5479,"timeElapsed":1065641},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665076289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2831,"timeElapsed":1068473},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665079825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":1072009},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665085145,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5319,"timeElapsed":1077329},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665089817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4671,"timeElapsed":1082001},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665095993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4272,"timeElapsed":1088177},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665099634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3640,"timeElapsed":1091818},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665103785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4150,"timeElapsed":1095969},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665109777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5992,"timeElapsed":1101961},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665113337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3559,"timeElapsed":1105521},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665116778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3439,"timeElapsed":1108962},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665119553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2775,"timeElapsed":1111737},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665129137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9583,"timeElapsed":1121321},{"subjectID":"tch6oz8o04","prolificID":"67262696d52e874c50a42d8d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742162776c921aa20c6e9c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665132769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":1124953}]